Hemang Shah

iOS Engineer

hemangshah.in@gmail.com

Summary

Six years of extensive experience in native iOS applications development along with a little in Android.

I can write code in Swift, Objective-C, and Java.

You can see my open source contributions on my Github profile and few of my Q&As on StackOverflow.

https://github.com/hemangshah

https://stackoverflow.com/users/1603234/hemang

Experience

Consultant at RAKSYS INDIA

April 2017 - Present

Working as Mobile Consultant (iOS) to build the apps which can be helpful to the citizens, residents, and the Government of Ras al Khaimah, UAE.

Consultant at iKiwiTech

May 2016 - March 2017 (11 months)

I worked as a consultant to handle various mobile/web application projects.

Consultant at Tecnics Integration Technologies Private Limited

November 2016 - December 2016 (2 months)

I went on-site at Ras al-Khaimah, the United Arab Emirates for a period of 1 month, I worked & consulted in iOS applications and made it available to the Apple's AppStore.

Sr. Software Engineer at Azilen Technologies Pvt Ltd

December 2015 - May 2016 (6 months)

Worked in a team while following AGILE methodologies for the development.

Sr. iOS Developer at AGILE Infoways Pvt Ltd

September 2014 - November 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Sr. iOS Developer | iOS Trainer

Sr. iOS Developer at iMOBDEV Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

January 2012 - September 2014 (2 years 9 months)

iPhone, iPod Touch and iPad Application Development

Software Engineer

June 2007 - August 2007 (3 months)

I worked there as a Visual Basic 6.0 developer and developed 3 inventory & education software for the clients in Bhavnagar City. I worked there in my vacation after the 2nd year of my graduation.

Education

Gujarat Technological University, Ahmedbabd

MCA, Computer Applications, 2009 - 2013

Shree Swaminarayan College of Computer Science

BCA, Computer Applications, 2006 - 2009

Shree Daxina Murti Vinay Mandir

Primary and Higher Secondary Education, 1993 - 2006

Hemang Shah

iOS Engineer

hemangshah.in@gmail.com



Contact Hemang on LinkedIn